<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vro on ParsingWings</title>
    <link>https://yanivnorman.com/tags/vro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vro on ParsingWings</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 19:00:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://yanivnorman.com/tags/vro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>vRO Logging Day-2 Operations with Event Log EBS topic</title>
      <link>https://yanivnorman.com/2016/08/23/vro-logging-day-2-operations-with-event-log-ebs-topic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 19:00:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanivnorman.com/2016/08/23/vro-logging-day-2-operations-with-event-log-ebs-topic/</guid>
      <description>vRA 7.x EBS is awesome !
While writing code, one should aspire to be as generic as possible, with simplicity being a key value – since it is not always possible to provide both simultaneously. this principal will meet us coders over-and-over. remember – Keep It Simple, Stupid! (or otherwise, KISS)
Sticking to this principle, I was trying to think about a generic way to log Day-2 operations in vRA, without being too specific to a type of request or setting up many EBS subscriptions for this customer request.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Encrypted vRA custom properties with vRO – Part I</title>
      <link>https://yanivnorman.com/2016/08/13/encrypted-vra-custom-properties-fun-with-vro-part-i/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2016 16:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yanivnorman.com/2016/08/13/encrypted-vra-custom-properties-fun-with-vro-part-i/</guid>
      <description>Recently I came across an Interesting customer request,
To be able to automate application installation in vRO, while database connection details will be provided by the end-user.
This being a production system, the requirement was to encrypt details, end-to-end.
While vRA does encrypt connection to vRO and vice-versa, values provided by end user to an IaaS blueprint are saved as is, plain-text. So to pass an encrypted value to a blueprint we need to encrypt the custom property.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>